 {

      "category":
            "Science",
      "questions":
          [
            {
               "answer": "Gagarin",
               "question": "Who was the first man to fly around the earth with a spaceship?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "The northern hemisphere",
               "question": "On which hemisphere were the most dinosaur skeletons found?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Blue",
               "question": "What color is cobalt?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Goodyear",
               "question": "Who invented vulcanized rubber?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Liver",
               "question": "What is the organ that is affected when one is suffering from hepatitis?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Telescope",
               "question": "Which device do we use to look at the stars?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Barometer",
               "question": "Which device is used to measure the air pressure?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Candela",
               "question": "Which unit indicates the light intensity?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Robert Oppenheimer",
               "question": "Who is the father of the atomic bomb?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Torricelli",
               "question": "Who invented the barometer?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Alan Shepard",
               "question": "Who was the first American in space?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Montgolfier",
               "question": "Two brothers invented the hot air balloon. What was their surname?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "James Watt",
               "question": "Who was the inventor of the steam engine?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The typewriter",
               "question": "Which device was invented by Henry Mill?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Aluminium",
               "question": "What is the lightest existing metal?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Ammoniac",
               "question": "What is the substance known by the chemical formula NH3?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Blue, yellow and red",
               "question": "What are the three primary colors?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Alexander Fleming",
               "question": "Who discoved one of the first antibiotics: penicillin ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Mercury",
               "question": "Which planet is nearest the sun?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Vostok 1",
               "question": "What was the name of Yuri Gagarin s space ship?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Diamond",
               "question": "Which natural substance is the hardest?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Hydrogen",
               "question": "What is the lightest chemical element?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Sirius",
               "question": "What is the brightest star in the northern hemisphere?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Uranus",
               "question": "Which planet was discovered by Frederik Herschel in 1781?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Asteroids",
               "question": "In astronomy, what are Pallas, Vesta and Davida?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Two kidneys",
               "question": "How many kidneys does a normal person have?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The symbol Pt",
               "question": "What is the chemical symbol for the Platinum element?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Five",
               "question": "How many eyes does a honeybee have? One, four or five?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Blue or purple",
               "question": "What is the color of giraffe tongue"
             }
          ]
    }